Seriously? This is way too much homework for anyone to have to do. I can't see me finishing
this even with help. I know. This homework is just as bad as we'd heard. This really sucks.
If I want to get this work over with, I need to start studying for my entrance exams.
Maybe I should have started prep school like Sanai. I probably would have been smart.
What do you think, Mugi? Well, maybe you should start around winter.
My family doesn't have the money. Hanabi. I'm gonna confess after I finish the homework.
Then I will too! Are you for real? Let's go at the same time.
In the end, it's about the momentum.
Última
abby
Well, don't I go to the end of it Raw.
Alah
A
It's a
got
a
Music
It's on
a
not
it's?
To be continued...
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's perfectly fine.
Atsiya!
Jeez, where have you been?
Hey there, Sinai.
Wow.
They're perfect for each other.
Sorry, I'm not familiar with the area.
You're bad at directions.
I remember.
You didn't have to come to the next town over just to take this summer course.
But this is where you are.
Ah, damn.
Our eyes just met.
Stop.
Hey, you always keep your hair so long, don't you?
How come?
Sinai has become even more beautiful.
I reconnected with her at our relative's funeral.
I hadn't seen her in six years.
She wasn't like any of the other girls in my class.
I don't have any siblings or very many friends.
She's really my only cousin.
What?
Atsiya Kirishima?
That's me.
Oh, damn it.
She's looking at me right now.
You're...
You're huge!
That's insane!
You used to be like this small!
Man, you've grown!
She...
She remembered me.
Sinai...
You've grown a lot, too.
Impressive.
Really?
I haven't changed at all.
You're beautiful.
Let's date.
Sinai couldn't have looked more disgusted with what I said.
Right.
Flashback over.
Sinai has become even more beautiful.
Are you going to become an actress?
What?
No.
I plan on going to college.
I'm persistent with her.
I don't give up.
I know Sinai has a crush that's too much for her.
I just don't care.
So then you're telling me you have a crush from your high school?
That's fine, then.
Why is that?
I mean, that's not the only crush you'll ever have.
And besides, it doesn't seem like it's going to work out anyway.
I can tell by the way you've been moping around here lately.
I'm just another helpful and concerned friend.
And a male relative to Boot.
That's why I want to know everything about Sinai.
Who I like.
It's a girl.
Understand?
I'll never have feelings for you.
Sinai.
Do you really like her because she's actually a girl?
And it's not working out because of that?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm not very good with complicated issues.
Maybe I'm insensitive.
So, let's see.
This is the first time you've actually fallen in love with someone.
Well, that makes me happy for you.
And if you like her so much, then I do too.
Okay?
Don't you see?
I probably hate all guys.
But you really don't hate me, do you?
Which means then, you're looking at me as the individual person, Atsuya Kirishima.
Basically, gender doesn't really come into any play between us.
Yeah, but look.
I don't need to put any gender labels on you.
You're my cousin.
Yes, but do you like her because you've given her a label to wear?
No.
Well, then that still means I have a chance with you.
Damn.
Our eyes met.
Did I study?
Of course I did.
Technically.
We're both serious students.
And we're both in the honor program.
You scared?
Yeah.
I'm like...
Really terrified.
I don't want to hear her answer.
Though I know it's a no.
You can pretend I'm her if you'd like to.
What the...
Why did I mention that?
What's gotten into me?
There's no reason to say that.
That was our original arrangement.
After all.
Pretend?
Just me?
It's okay.
It's fine.
What?
I don't get what you're saying right now.
Tell me.
I won't know if you don't say something.
Maybe we...
Maybe he's feeling the same thing.
It's just...
I don't know when it started.
But lately it seems...
I can't imagine you as her.
Does that mean...
He possibly...
Oh God.
I don't know what to say about any of that.
Why?
Come on.
I need to say something to him.
Well...
I guess.
We've both decided we're gonna do this.
We'll just have to see what happens.
And that was it.
That was when I realized.
It was different.
And I had also stopped comparing Mugi with brother like that.
I regarded them separately.
This is far enough.
I'm good now.
Thanks for walking me.
Hmm.
Summer is so short.
And we can't rewind time.
We'll be right back.
But...
Brother!
Huh?
When did you start wearing glasses?
Well, do I look good in them?
Yeah.
It makes you look like a real teacher.
Congrats.
On your exam.
Yeah, you too.
Thanks, but mine was just a silly high school entrance exam.
That's still no easy feat.
Yeah, but you realized what your dream was.
That's great.
You're a certified teacher now.
What?
Seriously?
You're crying now?
I mean, it made me realize how much you've grown up.
You know that?
Man, there you go treating me like a kid again.
Oh, what?
Hey, you remember?
The time you got lost on that big snow day?
We walked home, holding hands together.
Yeah, but that seems like a long time ago.
Oh, come on.
Just a day.
Just to your house.
What?
That's too embarrassing.
I have so many fond memories.
Most of them are so trivial.
But precious memories to me.
I'll treasure them all my life.
Have you remembered any of them?
The sheer thought of that happening?
That means I can go on living.
I'm not exaggerating in the least about that.
There's nobody better than you.
And the whole entire world.
No matter how warped or clumsy it was,
I have loved as hard as I can.
No, I won't run anymore.
Finally.
Homework is done.
Hmm.
You'll do it tomorrow afternoon?
I'll go at night then.
Let's confess it all.
You mean get rejected?
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
But this is good.
Not being alone.
We'll fail together.
Hmm.
You're right.
Well, alright.
Let's meet back here tomorrow.
Say around 10pm.
Hmm.
This is hard.
I can't seem to look at Mookie's face directly.
Why is this happening now?
Well, I'll see you.
Oh, God.
Seriously?
What is this?
My face feels warm.
Good night.
What the hell?
Was that his way of cheering me on?
But I guess...
All this excitement...
Helps stop my shaking, at least.
I feel weird getting excited with Mookie.
But...
I don't hate it.
Maybe...
I can move forward after all.
That was strange.
I had a dream about holding hands.
I wonder who it was with.
Hey there, Mookie.
Well, what's going on?
It's a little hot today, huh?
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for coming here to meet me.
It's fine.
I'll do anything for my dear sweet student.
Besides, you're one of the special ones.
You need advice about your future?
Well, here I go.
I'm about to get rejected by her.
She still keeps it up, doesn't she?
That mask of hers.
Not that.
Well, you see, I...
Huh?
Well, what is it then?
Uh...
I'm getting a bit thirsty out here.
Let's go to a cafe.
It seems I've let her take the lead.
Did you get a tan, Mookie?
Huh?
You think?
That's terrific.
I was really worried I wouldn't get a tan.
That's almost hurtful in a strange way.
There's nothing wrong with being pale and white.
It has its appeal as well.
Oh, no.
It's more than a little pale in my case.
I'm like a walking corpse in daylight.
Is that so?
I wouldn't be too harsh about it.
I think girls prefer that.
Is she for real?
Does she like pop idols?
Or is she more of a jock groupie?
She must like the pretty ones.
Though she did sleep with some old bald dude.
So then...
What about me?
Miss Minagawa...
I love you.
Or I used to.
Well, I knew that.
I knew you knew that.
Well, that part I didn't know about.
But you're a liar.
Look, I like you, Mugi.
I do.
Don't get excited.
I know that you're always lying to people.
That's not relative.
I know.
Because I've watched you.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Pull back already.
Don't do this.
Stop being an idiot.
She's someone...
I can...
Never have.
That's why I liked her.
She wasn't obtainable.
I couldn't have her.
Then...
What about...
That's why.
I know there's no way...
You care about me.
But she's right in front of me.
Looking...
Right at me.
It's not a lie.
You must have known.
I've always cared about you two.
But I'd already...
Decided...
I would never leave her alone again.
For the record...
I do know.
Huh?
And what is that?
What you really are!
That you're a horrible, promiscuous, broken narcissist.
And no matter what...
You'll never fall in love with anyone.
But that your men must follow different rules.
Because you're not satisfied unless you are loved.
But...
Even my feelings for you...
Don't matter.
Because really...
It doesn't have to be me.
You're so cute.
Then why bother following me all the way here?
Yeah.
I know this is my own dumbass fault.
It's like an NPC villager confronting the final boss.
I'll admit that.
Because I know...
You'll never care for me.
I'm aware of this imbalance.
She has it all.
And her paper-thin words and fake acting hold no value for me.
But still...
I'm weak.
And the reason I'm here...
Because maybe...
I might just be here first.
And...
I want to change you.
Hey.
Hanabi.
You've finished already?
All that homework?
Yes.
Teacher.
It feels like I haven't seen you in a while.
Well...
Since we're on summer break, that would until not getting to see you as much.
Huh?
Brother, do you know yet?
Have you figured out the reason why I asked you here?
What?
No.
What is it?
I have no idea why.
I like that most about you.
You know?
Hey now.
You're making fun.
I used to like you.
But not anymore?
That's a lie.
I still like you.
Huh?
That's what I wanted to tell you tonight.
Since when?
Has he really just been so clueless for all this time?
But I love how quickly he takes me seriously after finding out he's great.
I'd say...
For a long, long time now.
And I love how considerate he is of other people's feelings.
The more I put it into words, the more I feel.
I love his voice.
And his face.
I love his gestures and the way he talks.
I love how good he thinks and all of his compassion.
But above all of that,
I love how you just accept me.
When it's truly important.
Hannah.
I know.
Don't worry.
I'll be okay.
Promise.
I'm only shaking because I know it's not me.
When was the last time I got to cry this hard before?
When I feel how tightly he holds me with his arms wrapped around me,
it makes me realize that this is the first and last time,
which makes me cry more.
He holds me like he's never going to let go.
He's so good to me.
The fact that he cares about me makes me happy.
Even if it's not romantic.
And so my long-lasting, unrequited love...
Hannah.
Thank you.
Ended.
It's okay.
It'll be okay.
I know I'll be able to move on now.
I'm sure of it.
I know I can change.
Because I'm not...
Alone.